<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<slides>
    <slide>
        <image>carousel/images/slides/hbo.png</image>
        <hoverHTML><![CDATA[
            Learn more about working at HBO
        ]]></hoverHTML>
        <mainHTML><![CDATA[
            <h2>HOME BOX OFFICE</h2>
            <p>Just as HBO is a company noted for its commitment to excellence in the products and services it delivers to consumers, it makes the extra effort to create a work environment in which fairness, equity, trust, and individual responsibility are valued. The Company believes that talented, dedicated and enthusiastic employees are by far HBO's most valuable asset.</p>
            <div class='button with-separator'><a href='http://www.timewarner.com/careers/areas-of-operation/our-divisions/hbo/' target="_blank">More Info</a></div><div class='button with-separator'><a href='https://careers.timewarner.com/1033/ASP/TG/cim_searchresults.asp?PartnerId=391&SiteId=36&Function=LinkQuery&LinkId=365' target="_blank">Jobs</a></div>
        ]]></mainHTML>
    </slide>

    
    <slide>
        <image>carousel/images/slides/time.png</image>
        <hoverHTML><![CDATA[
            Learn more about working at Time Inc.
        ]]></hoverHTML>
        <mainHTML><![CDATA[
            <h2>TIME INC.</h2>
            <p>Talent is the cornerstone of Time Inc.'s success and its future. Are you a top performer in search of a culture of excellence and integrity, where the best is expected of you every day and the company gives its best back to you? If the answer is yes, we'd like to know you better.</p>
            <div class='button with-separator'><a href='http://www.timewarner.com/careers/areas-of-operation/our-divisions/time-inc/' target="_blank">More Info</a></div><div class='button with-separator'><a href='https://careers.timewarner.com/1033/ASP/TG/cim_searchresults.asp?PartnerId=391&SiteId=36&Function=LinkQuery&LinkId=366' target="_blank">Jobs</a></div>
        ]]></mainHTML>
    </slide>
    <slide>
        <image>carousel/images/slides/tw.png</image>
        <hoverHTML><![CDATA[
            Learn more about working at Time Warner Corporate
        ]]></hoverHTML>
        <mainHTML><![CDATA[
            <h2>TIME WARNER COPRORATE</h2>
            <p>Time Warner Corporate is headquartered in New York City. With a variety of opportunities, we aim to attract and retain the most talented and diverse individuals possessing skills and experience in many different disciplines. Many departments at Time Warner Corporate engage in cross-divisional work, which involves partnering with one or more of our divisions on exciting projects. Collaboration between Time Warner Corporate and its divisions is key to our business and overall success.</p>
            <div class='button with-separator'><a href='#' target="_blank">More Info</a></div><div class='button with-separator'><a href='#' target="_blank">Jobs</a></div>
        ]]></mainHTML>
    </slide>

    <slide>
        <image>carousel/images/slides/turner.png</image>
        <hoverHTML><![CDATA[
            Learn more about working at Turner
        ]]></hoverHTML>
        <mainHTML><![CDATA[
            <h2>TURNER BROADCASTING SYSTEM, INC.</h2>
            <p>People are drawn to Turner Broadcasting System, Inc. because it is an exciting, enlightened, socially responsible company with which to build a career. Our company creates and programs branded news, entertainment, animation and young adult media environments on television and other platforms for consumers around the world.</p>
            <div class='button with-separator'><a href='http://timewarner.com/careers/areas-of-operation/our-divisions/turner-broadcasting-system/' target="_blank">More Info</a></div><div class='button with-separator'><a href='https://careers.timewarner.com/1033/ASP/TG/cim_searchresults.asp?PartnerId=391&SiteId=36&Function=LinkQuery&LinkId=368' target="_blank">Jobs</a></div>
        ]]></mainHTML>
    </slide>

    <slide>
        <image>carousel/images/slides/wb.png</image>
        <hoverHTML><![CDATA[
            Learn more about working at Warner Bros.
        ]]></hoverHTML>
        <mainHTML><![CDATA[
            <h2>WARNER BROS. ENTERTAINMENT</h2>
            <p>At Warner Bros. Entertainment, we maintain a culture of creativity, professional growth, and community that attracts the world's brightest stars and keeps them shining throughout their careers. When the best opportunities in the industry meet some of the most brilliant people in the world, they form a powerful workforce that can only be described as Warner Bros. Entertainment.</p>
            <div class='button with-separator'><a href='http://timewarner.com/careers/areas-of-operation/our-divisions/warner-bros-entertainment/' target="_blank">More Info</a></div><div class='button with-separator'><a href='https://careers.timewarner.com/1033/ASP/TG/cim_searchresults.asp?PartnerId=391&SiteId=36&Function=LinkQuery&LinkId=410' target="_blank">Jobs</a></div>
        ]]></mainHTML>
    </slide>
    
    


</slides>